并提醒司机和行人注意安全…
citing the danger to both drivers and pedestrians...
不是本地风格 欧式喷漆吗？
Not from around here. European design?
的确很漂亮 但是过头了
Sure it's pretty. Too pretty.
你犯了个大错
Big mistake.
噢…伙计
Oh... dude.
你刮我的漆
You scratch my paint
我要你的命
I scratch yours.
嘿 这不是女式轻骑么
Hey, cherry moped.
呃 这款轻骑配有双化油器 百公里加速只要3.5秒
Uh, this moped has dual carbs and can go 0 to 60 in 3.5 seconds.
呃 杰克
Uh, Jack
女士的属性可是个人隐私
a lady's vital stats are her own business.
嘿！你叫尼克对吧？
Hey! Nick, right?
其实…是杰克
Actually... it's Jack.
杰克 不好意思 我叫塞拉
Jack. Sorry. I am Sierra.
我…我知道
I... I know.
你说过要带我去兜风的是吗？
You once offered to take me for a ride?
我…当然说过 随时恭候
Of... course I did, at any time.
我是你的保镖 小鬼
I'm your guardian, kiddo.
不是电灯泡
Not your wingman.
那么 现在如何？
So, how about now?
呃…
Uh...
嘿 世界真小啊
Hey, small world.
呃…我们在聊天
Em... been having a conversation.
这位啦啦队长可能很乐意欣赏 你和四轮肌肉车过招
Cheer captain here might enjoy watching you take on four wheels of muscle car.
你是想跟我…赛车吗？
Are you challenging me... to a race?
理解力不错嘛 笨鸟 敢不敢应战？
You catch on quick, paunch. What do you say?
呃…
Uh...
你…你没让我回答
You... you didn't let me answer.
对
Nope.
阿尔茜 我们可以赢得他灰头土脸
Arcee, we can smoke him.
没错
Yeape.
呃…你真不近人情
Uh... you just don't get it.
规矩不是我定的 杰克
I don't make the rules, Jack.
是擎天柱
Optumis does.
守则第一条还记得不
And rule No.1, in case you missed it
绝不能在个人享乐上滥用能力
never abuse power for a personal game.
也包括马力
And that includes horse power.
文斯 赛车可能不太适合我
Vince, maybe racing isn't such a good idea.
明白
hahaha, figured.
你把摩托车当成宝贝一样骑
You ride around like your bike's something special.
可它只是辆笨蛋老破车 丑到极点了！
But it's just a chunky clunky trike, and ugly.
够了 这小丑死定了
That's it. The yahoo is going down.
喔 守则第一条不管了？
Wow, what happened to rule No.1?
守则也是人定的 下不为例
Gets bent. Just this once.
我说姑娘们 你们那个姓达比的 他…
Yo, girls, your pal Darby, he's...
随时应战 小蚊子
Ready when you are, Vinny.
司机农场旁边的土道 一小时后
Dirt road by Trucker's Ranch. One hour.
从这儿到下一个里程牌 预备…出发！
From here to the next mile marker. Ready? Go.
还真公平啊
Oh, that was fair.
呃…阿尔茜？
Eh... Arcee?
只是A就便宜他了 杰克
Winning isn't enough, Jack.
要让他欲哭无泪
You wanna make him cry.
什么？
What?
一马当先！
Outstanding!
喔 嘿 现在可不可以顺势带塞拉在街上兜一圈？
Oh, hey, now it might be a good time to offer Sierra quick once around the block?
别得寸进尺
Don't push it.
啊 打击
Ah, Breakdown
威震天的身体状况有点起色没有？
has there been any change in Megatron's condition?
呃 只是脸色好了点
Um, only cosmetic.
好吧 我相信你和那个神医已经尽力了
Well, I am sure that you and the good doctor have been doing everything in your power.
击倒哪儿去了？
Where is Knock Out?
你能猜到某个臭皮匠对我做了什么吗？
Can you believe what some skinjob did to me?
你又去和人类飙车了 对不对？
You have been street racing among the humans again, haven't you?
我不只是辆车 还是辆狂热的赛车
I'm not only an automobile, I am an automobile enthusiast.
我力求军纪严明 击倒
I do strive to run a tight ship, Knock Out.
我强烈建议你 下次你决定开小差的时候 要征得本人的许可
I would strongly suggest that you seek my permission next time you decide to disappear on one of your little jobs.
没问题 指挥官先生
No worries, Herr Commandant.
你应该叫陛下
It is lord to you.
等威震天驾崩之后再说吧
Only if Megatron takes a nosedive.
有朝一日我们的主人苏醒
The day our master emerges from stasis
我将把头衔拱手相让
I will graciously relinquish the title.
但我认为几乎没这个可能
But I believe that outcome is unlikely.
目前的医疗水平不过如此
Something to do with the quality of medical care around here.
继续抛光吧
So continue buffing.
我们真心希望威震天在追悼会上红光满面
We do want Megatron looking his best for the memorial.
先给我抛个光
Buff this.
别告诉任何人
Not a word to anyone.
我们的小秘密
Our little secret.
伙计！嗡 嗡 嗡…获胜者是…
Dude! vong... and the winner is?
神子 谁告诉你的？
Miko, who told you?
你开玩笑吧？全校都知道了！
You kidding? It's all over school!
你让那个叫文斯的学校霸王输得找不着北了
You beat the pants off that blowhard bully Vince.
你们得严格保密 尤其不能告诉擎天柱
You guys have to keep this on the DL, especially from Optimus.
嘿 我正找你呢
Hey, I've been looking for you.
那比赛可真过瘾 我一直在喊…
The race, how great was that, I was like...
耶！加油 杰克！
Yeah, go Jack!
也…没什么
It... it was no big deal.
算你说对了
You got that right.
如果你觉得能跑过那些高手的话？
If you think you can run with the big boys
今晚11点 赛道见
the circuit, tonight, 11pm.
你答应了？
You agreed to what?
那是个地下赛车俱乐部
It was some kind of secret racing club.
我也不清楚 我没得选
But I don't know, I had no choice.
塞拉当时就在我旁边
Sierra was standing right there.
你总会有选择权的 杰克
You always have a choice, Jack.
你听不懂什么叫“下不为例”吗？
And what part of "just this once" did you not understand?
我知道…对不起
I know... I'm sorry.
可…我们会去的 对吗？
But... we are on, right?
我们不去
We are not on.
击倒 红蜘蛛又找不着你了
Knok Out, Starsceam's been looking for you again
你在哪儿？
where did you go?
自然是出来兜风了
Out for a little drive.
在几个城市之间转转
I just rode from town to town
侦察侦察…
sniffing around until...
机会总是能找上门来的
the next opportunity presents itself.
拉夫
Raf
呃…可以把大黄蜂借我一个小时吗？
uh... is there anyway I could borrow Bumblebee for one hour?
杰克 赛车违反规定 你是知道的
Jack, you know racing is against the rules.
擎天柱知道了怎么办？
What if Optimus found out?
但是拉夫 他得去泡妞
But Raf, he's gotta get the girl
顺便打黑除恶…
and beat the bully...
那…
Well...
求你了 拉夫 下不为例…
Come on, Raf, just this once...
摩托车送修了
Bike is in the shop.
各位车手 准备好了吗？
Circuit drivers, are you ready?
开足马力 但要遵守规则
Make it beep but keep it clean!
准备 5 4 3 2 1！
Fire on 5, 4, 3, 2, 1!
那个汽车人叫…大黄蜂
The Autobot they called... Bumblebee.
那是什么 小蜂？
What was that, Bee?
慢着 我认识那车
Wait, I know that car.
什么…
What the...
你能甩掉他吗 小蜂？
Can you lose it, Bee?
你说什么？
What do you say?
但愿那是“同意”的意思
I hope that means yes.
我可不想呼叫基地请求增援
Cause I'd rather not have to call base for backup.
有谁看到杰克了吗?
Anyone's seen Jack?
上次之后…
Not since...
就再没见过
we last saw him.
他们在赛车 对吧？
They are racing, aren't they?
下不为例
Just this once.
你知情吗？
Did you know about this?
不…大概 知道一点
No... maybe. A little.
你们被击倒盯上了？
You are being chased by Knock Out?
听上去像是个霸天虎
That sounds like a Decepticon.
小蜂 不要交战
Bee, do not engage.
你的首要任务是保证杰克的安全
Your first priority is to keep Jack safe.
到时候我再教训他
Until I get my hands on him.
小心 地滑
Slick.
我们大概甩掉他了 小蜂
I think we lost him, Bee.
喔 别开这种玩笑啊！
Oh, you gotta be kidding me!
达比！
Darby!
文斯 你得离开这儿 算你赢了 行吗？
Vince, you have to get out of here, you win, okay?
恭喜你！快走！
Congratulations! Now, go!
不 不 言出必行 笨蛋
No, no, start or backoff, loser
必须跑完比赛！
we are finishing this race!
不想在终点线出丑是吗？行！
Don't wanna take to the finish line? Fine!
那我们就地解决！
Then we got something to settle right here! Right now!
怎么回事？你要干…
What's going on? What are you...
打击 你绝对想不到我抓到了什么
Breakdown, you'll never guess what I'm packing -
是大黄蜂的人类伙伴
Bumblebee's human friend.
等那个汽车人来营救的时候…
And, when the Autobot attempts to stage a rescue...
就给他来个致命“打击”
He has a... Breakdown.
小蜂 他跑了！
Bee, he's getting away!
我…我听不懂你的话！
I... I can't understand you!
听着 我可不是拉夫
Look, I am not Raf
你能不能…鸣笛一声代表坏消息
can't you just... honk once for bad news
两声代表好消息？
and honk twice for good news?
杰克 我们得好好谈谈
Jack, we need to have a little chat.
等等吧 阿尔茜
Later, Arcee.
文斯被那个狡猾的跑车虎子抓走了
Vince's got snatched by the slick sportscar Con.
击倒怎么会抓个无名氏呢？
What would Knock Out want with a random human?
也许他把文斯当成大黄蜂的人类伙伴了
He probably mistook Vince for Bumblebee's human friend.
可连我都不算是大黄蜂的人类伙伴
I'm not even Bumblebee's human friend.
我不知道 管他为什么抓人 文斯有麻烦了！
I don't know, it doesn't matter why he took him... Vince is in trouble!
好吧 算文斯倒霉
Oh well, tough break for Vince.
隔板！
Bulkhead!
怎么了 这家伙不是个混蛋吗？
Why, I heard this guy is a jerk.
我不否认 但他是无辜的
No arguement there, but the guy is also innocent.
文斯不该被虎子蹂躏
Vince doesn't deserve to get crushed by Cons.
上车
Hop on.
他们早该回来了
They should have called off by now.
你觉得大黄蜂会有事吗？
You think Bumblebee is okay?
别担心 拉夫
Don't worry, Raf
隔板不会让杰克和小蜂出事的
Bulkhead won't let anything happen to Jack or Bee.
我们应该跟擎天柱说实话
We should just tell Optimus the truth.
绝对不行
Absolutely not.
我们说好的
We made a deal.
假装没事就行
Just act completely normal.
拉夫 神子
Raf, Miko
你们知道其他人去哪儿了吗？
do either of you know where the others have gone?
什么？不 长官 我们不知道
Why, no, sir. We do not know.
神子说得对 我们不知道
Miko is correct. We do not know.
我们怎么会知道？
Why would we know?
呃…
Hum...
大黄蜂叫帮手来了
Bumblebee brought company.
提高警惕 各位 可能是个陷阱
On your guard, boys, could be a trap.
记住 别开火
Remember, no shooting.
安全起见
Speaking of safety
你该在这儿下车
here is where you get off.
那个两轮儿的去哪儿了？
Hmm... Where's the two-wheeler?
嘿！当心我的喷漆！
Hey! Watch the paint!
好姑娘！
That's my girl.
呃 打击
Uh... Breakdown
友情提醒你一下 场面有点乱
in case you are looking for me, thing's got messy.
我开溜了
So I hit the road.
一天剐蹭一次已经受够了
One scrape is enough for today.
吃灰去吧
Eat my dust.
擎天柱 击倒有人质
Optimus, Knock Out has a hostage.
明白
Understood.
你知道换零件多麻烦吗？
Do you know how hard that is to replace?
擎天柱…是我的错
Optimus... This was my fault.
必须立刻把这男孩带到安全地区
We must get this boy to safety immediately.
认错另选时间 你们都有责任
Explanations can come later, from all of you.
怎么了…出什么事了？
How did... What happened?
有人在桥下抓住你
Someguys... jumped you under the bridge
想拉你入伙
they tossed you into their trunk
像是某种入会仪式
must be some kind of initiation.
真的吗？
Really?
没错 我发现你…
Yeah, I found you...
晕倒在路边
knocked out by the side of the road.
我…得承认 有了今晚的经历
I... I gotta be honest, after what I saw tonight
我觉得赛车真的不适合我
I'm thinking racing just isn't my thing.
这还用说 达比
I hear you, Darby
骑脚踏车是赢不了比赛的
hard to win a race driving a pedal car.
击倒！我说的还不清楚吗？
Knock Out! Was I not clear?
你竟敢再次无视我的命令！
You have defied my order yet again.
我知错了 红蜘蛛指挥官
My mistake, commander Starscream.
我也吸取了教训
But I've learned my lesson.
还付出了代价
And paid the price.
叫我陛下！
It is Lord!
而且你付出多少代价 由我说了算
And you have paid when I say you have paid.
别担心 对你的惩罚只是…面子问题
Do not worry, Your punishment shall be mearly... cosmetic.
不 别刮喷漆 除了喷漆什么都行 不！！
No... not the finish, anything but the finish, No!!
那个…杰克 你有时间去兜风吗？
So, Jack, do you have time for that ride?
呃 我…很抱歉 塞拉 现在不行
Uh... I... I'm sorry, Sierra, I can't right now.
没关系 那我们就…回头见吧
No problem, I guess I'll just see you around.
上车
Hop on.
喔…真的吗？
Oh... Really?
下不为例
Just this once.